<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AllIn</string>

    <string name="Plants">Plants</string>
    <string name="Pets">Pets</string>
    <string name="Decoration">Decoration</string>
    <string name="Workshops">Workshops</string>

    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>
    <string name="mail">workshopstudio@allin.com</string>
    <string name="Home">Home</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


    <string name="w1_materials">Epoxy resin\nHardener\nMixing sticks\nMolds\nPigments and dyes\nGlitter and other embellishments\nSafety gloves\nSafety glasses\nRespirator</string>
    <string name="w1_description">Epoxy resin is a versatile material that can be used to create a variety of projects,
        such as jewelry, home décor, and even furniture. In this workshop, participants will learn the basics of working with epoxy resin,
        including how to mix and pour the resin, add color and pigments, and avoid common mistakes.</string>

    <string name="w2_materials">Acrylic paint or tempera paint\nPaint brushes\nWater containers\nPaper\nAprons or old clothes</string>
    <string name="w2_description">Painting is a great way for kids to express their creativity and have fun.
        In this workshop, kids will learn different painting techniques, such as how to use brushes, mix colors, and create different textures.
        They will also get to take home their own painted masterpiece.</string>

    <string name="w3_materials">Construction paper or fabric\nScissors\nGlue\nMarkers and crayons\nDoilies or other embellishments</string>
    <string name="w3_description">Appliqué is a fun and easy way for kids to create art.
        In this workshop, kids will learn how to cut out shapes from paper or fabric and glue them onto a background to create a picture.
        They will also get to use their own creativity to come up with their own unique designs.</string>

    <string name="w4_materials">Acrylic paint, watercolor paint or oil paint\nPaint brushes\nCanvas or paper\nEasel\nApron or old clothes</string>
    <string name="w4_description">Whether you are a beginner or experienced painter,
        this workshop is a great way to improve your skills and learn new techniques.
        In this workshop, you will learn about different painting mediums, such as acrylics, watercolors, and oils.
        You will also get to work on your own painting project.</string>

    <string name="w5_materials">"Clay\nWater\nPottery tools\nKiln</string>
    <string name="w5_description">Working with clay is a great way to get your hands dirty and create something beautiful.
        In this workshop, you will learn the basics of hand-building with clay, such as how to coil, pinch, and slab build.
        You will also get to create your own unique piece of pottery.</string>

</resources>